單身美眉看過來
All the single ladies, all the single ladies
All the single ladies
把手放在空中甩
Now put your hands up
ㄜㄜㄜㄜ～
Eh eh eh eh~
我金罵沒ㄤ 金罵沒ㄤ
I have no husband, have no husband right now
雙人枕頭剩我一人
Cute couple was cut in half
(單身美眉)
(Single Ladies)
金罵沒ㄤ 金罵沒ㄤ
Have no husband, have no husband
呷飯呷麵順便來聞香
Come to me when you are hungry
(單身美眉)
(Single Ladies)
恢復了單身，重返俱樂部懷抱
Up in the club, we just woke up
我們的派對，盡情的享受玩開
I'm doing my own lil thing
前男友卻死纏不放
And you decided to dip, now you wanna trip
只因有個男孩鎖定了我
Cuz another brutha noticed me
我們一起搖擺舞動
I'm up on him, he up on me
花心前男友走著瞧
Don't pay him any attention
記取三年的教訓，感情讓我很受傷
Kept crying my tears, for three good years
你再也不能對我發飆
You can't be mad at me
千萬不通 千萬不通
Please stop, please stop
我不是彼款請裁的人
I'm not that kind of girl
(單身美眉)
(Single Ladies)
千萬不通 千萬不通
Please stop, please stop
愛我愛甲褲底破一洞
Don't love me to be brokey-panty
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
(褲底破一洞)
(Brokey-panty)
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
(褲底破一洞)
(Brokey-panty)
ㄜㄜㄜㄜ～
Eh eh eh eh~
我係水某沒ㄤ 水某沒ㄤ
I'm a pretty widow, pretty widow
芋頭番薯攏流口水
Every men loves me
(單身美眉)
(Single Ladies)
我金罵沒ㄤ 金罵沒ㄤ
I have no husband, have no husband right now
妖嬌美麗呼你看到脫窗
My beauty can pop your eyes out
(單身美眉)
(Single Ladies)
(單身美眉看過來)
(All the single ladies, all the single ladies)
(All the single ladies)
(把手放在空中甩)
(Now put your hands up)
牠不是普通的石斑
This is no ordinary fish
牠是北海小英雄的朋友
This is Luffy, friend of "Vicky the Vicking"
魯夫啊
海賊王的魯夫你知道嗎
You know, Luffy from "One Piece"?
他抓來的耶
He's the one that caught it!
我是北部有名聲 南部有出名
I am wife of the late Master Fly Spirit,
蒼蠅師的老婆
a Master with a legendary reputation
Wife of Master Fly Spirit
蒼蠅師的老婆
我金罵沒ㄤ 金罵沒ㄤ
I have no husband, have no husband right now
雙人枕頭剩我一人
Cute couple was cut in half
(單身美眉)
(Single Ladies)
金罵沒ㄤ 金罵沒ㄤ
Have no husband, have no husband
呷飯呷麵順便來聞香
Come to me when you are hungry
(單身美眉)
(Single Ladies)
ㄜㄜㄜㄜ～
Eh eh eh eh~
如果你心動，那就為我帶上定情戒
If you liked it, then you should've put a ring on it
前男友可別忌妒，新女性獨立自主
Don't be mad once you see that he wants it
如果你愛我，那就為我帶上定情戒
If you liked it, then you should've put a ring on it
蒼蠅師的老婆
Wife of Master Fly Spirit